

Elmehdi AGUENDICH

Software Engineer

Salé, Morocco +212 631 232 736 mehdi_aguendich@protonmail.com

in LinkedIn GitHub Tortfolio

SUMMARY

Junior Software Engineer with one year of professional experience in the development of software solutions, including one dedicated to internal documents and customer relationship management. Proficient in Java, TypeScript and REST API. Machine Learning and Computer Vision enthusiast.

EXPERIENCE _

INOVAR

Apr 2022 - Sept 2022 · 5 mos / Remote

PEGA System Architect, Full-time remote

- PEGA System Architect certification course.
- Software solution evolution and maintenance using PEGA System tools.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

PEGA Appstudio | PEGA Devstudio

ASATECHNO CONSULTING

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 · 3 mos / Kénitra, Morocco

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INTERNSHIP

- · Work environment preparation.
- Collaborative teamwork using a CI/CD tool.
- Insurance sector software solutions evolution and maintenance.
- Documentation of all tasks mentioned above.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

• CI/CD | Java | Play | React | Scala | Scala.js

• Eclipse | GitLab CI/CD | Intelli] IDEA | SBT

ISO QUAL TECH.

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 · 6 mos / Salé, Morocco

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INTERNSHIP

• Enterprise internal commercial flow management, software solution design and implementation.

TECHNOLOGY STACK:

• Angular 11 | exceljs | PDF.js | REST | Spring (Boot, Data, Security) | UML

• Eclipse | Microsoft Excel | MongoDB | MySQL | VS Code

EDUCATION ___

ÉCOLE MAROCAINE DES SCIENCES DE L'INGÉNIEUR

2017-2021 / Rabat, Morocco

STATE ENGINEER DEGREE, COMPUTER SCIENCE AND NETWORKS OPTION: MIAGE

INSTITUT D'AGRICULTURE ET VETERINARIAT HASSAN II

2014-2017 / Rabat, Morocco

CORE CURRICULUM OPTION: AGRONOMY

LYCÉE MOULAY TAYEB EL ALAOUI 2012-2014 / Salé, Morocco

BACCALAUREAT DEGREE, OPTION: MATHEMATICAL SCIENCES -A-

SKILLS _

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT *Proficient:* Angular 12 | Java | Python | Spring (Boot, Security) | TypeScript

Familiar: GitLab | MongoDB | MySQL | Next.js | Node.js | Spring (Data) | UML

LANGUES *Native:* Arabic *Professionnel:* French | English | German

INTERESTS _

• Reading: Crime and Punishment (Fyodor Dostoevsky) | Le Monde de Sophie (Jostein Gaarder).

- Excursion: Excursion to the summit of "La Cathédrale".
- Music : Music theory and 5th year guitar diploma. Conservatoire Dar El Baroud, Salé.